You don't want the borders
opened either, do you?
You can be honest with me.
After all,
you were desperate enough
to go to a pirate to
buy the weapons you needed
to fight their kind.
It's almost as if
everything's a big joke, Tom.
You must be hurting after
the loss of your arms broker,
Dothamingo, and now with
your veil of anonymity gone,
you have no choice but
to deal with us directly.
You do realize we have the upper hand
when you're in a position like that.
You really shouldn't be making
such unreasonable demands.
You've seen Wano, yes?
We're as self-sufficient
as they come, friend.
The people of Wano look awfully happy.
I'm sure you've noticed that yourselves.
Although there's one thing
we're always in need of,
and that's more power in my hands.
My request was a warship before.
But now, we demand Dr. Vegapunk!
No, we can't!
I wasn't asking, I'm telling you.
Celestial dragons, the navy.
You must have caught on by now that the
land of Wano fears none of these things.
Even if you pulled your
forces together to attack us.
You'd never be able to bring
our nation to its knees.
I have Kaido on my side.
I am unstoppable.
One dream, one wish.
If you want it, gotta go over the top.
Setting sail and heading for the unknown.
Cutting through the
winds and waves as I go.
Gotta keep it up, never stopping, no.
Cause I'm aiming to get there first, yeah.
It's all or nothing, no time to worry.
Do it later, right now I'm living free.
When your foes look like
they will overwhelm you.
It means your heart's saying
this is what you can't do.
Despite all that to run is not an option.
Once they're closed, they
feel the satisfaction.
You think I'm rude,
here's my appreciation.
When things are getting
tough, just gotta smile.
If you are going on your way.
And you're looking for
a fresh, brand new day.
Then make sure your only
thought you have is.
Yes, I can.
As you're on your way,
marks maps will be made.
Yes, with every step that you will take.
Just look at all you've been through.
Look ahead to new horizons in view.
Shining brightly, oh, who
knows what's waiting for you.
Dream living, that's the way.
Make like a hurricane.
Now, got to make your mark today.
One dream, one wish.
Your dreams don't run away.
Go for the knockout.
Over the top.
Lady Komurasaki is here.
Make way.
I'm late, I know!
You had me worried.
Sorry I can't be waiting so long.
Well, let's get to work.
Kay!
Ah!
Lady Komonosaki is approaching!
The procession's coming!
How much longer?
That's a pretty hefty
crowd she's got riled up.
You think she's as pretty as they say?
This is nuts!
Hurry up!
I can't take it anymore!
I hate that bitch!
Komurasaki!
Looks like they want trouble.
Hey, stop!
It's too late now.
I have to murder her!
I'm being expelled from the capital.
It's all over for me!
If I'm destined to die anyway,
I'll take her down, too!
Stay away from the Oiran, you trash!
Why?
Why would she do this to me?
I wish to be by your side forever.
If only it were possible.
You want to be with an
old bag of bones like me?
If I have no choice but to stay
here as the Shogun's plaything,
then I would much rather have my
contract sold to a kind man such as you.
But the price of my freedom is
so steep, I fear it's impossible.
Forgive me.
I shouldn't have spoken up.
If the Shogun were to hear I said such
a thing, I would surely face his wrath.
You must not lose heart, dear.
Would that really bring
you true happiness?
Say the word and I, bingo,
shall make it happen.
You would do that for me?
I am delighted to hear it,
even if nothing comes to be.
What do you mean you can't pay me back?
Forgive us.
Do you take me for a fool?
Crying won't bail you
out, so just knock it off.
I'll take your house as
collateral for the overdue loan.
For you, m 'lady.
That is quite a lot.
I've never seen such wealth.
You can count it.
This is going to be the down payment so
that I may buy you from the pleasure hall.
It's not enough, but do hold on to it.
Please allow me to mark
this in the ledger.
There's no need to bother.
Only a fool would have
distrust in the woman he loves.
Your word will do just fine.
You're too kind.
Thank you.
I long for the day we go home together.
Don't cry.
I have a solution.
Allow me to organize the funeral for you.
I'll front the money until
you get back on your feet.
Stop with the crying already!
Oh, don't act surprised
that you owe me double!
You shouldn't expect a
favor to come without a fee!
Here is your money, my love. Incredible!
Though I fear I'd bear ill tidings.
What's wrong, my love?
I've heard that another man is interested
in buying my contract and
has put in a bid. Hey, what?
There's no time.
I need to gather more
money before it's too late.
What else can I sell around here?
I sold everything I own, Gomorrah Saki.
I'm so lucky to have met you.
Enough already.
That's the final straw.
I'm moving back home.
I can't take you anymore.
Do whatever you want.
Oh, darling.
Be right there.
I've abandoned my family for you.
Oh my, your health.
Take care of yourself, dear.
Don't you worry about me.
I can just tough it out.
Medicine is a waste of money.
The quicker I can get your payment,
the sooner we can live
together happily ever after.
Oh my goodness.
I am so lucky to have you.
My love, I dream of that day too.
Go, Murasaki.
The deed is done.
I may no longer have a place to live,
but I have all the money in hand.
We can build from scratch.
This is the final 500 gold coins.
You've been patient.
The day is finally here.
Let's go home.
What?
Apologies.
However, the oiron is unwell today.
That's quite unfortunate.
Regardless, please make sure
this gets into her hands.
I will return soon.
Komurasaki!
I've come to save you
from this wretched life!
You're free to come home with me at last!
I can't believe this guy.
Nice going, you old love-struck pervert!
All right, all right, everyone.
That's quite enough laughing!
Wrap it up.
Now go fetch her.
You realize she's expecting me?
We have both been looking
forward to this day.
Pathetic.
You really believed in all that crap?
She has enough money to free her.
I've been saving it up
for a while, actually.
Komunasaki's holding it.
Oh, bingo. It's you.
Ah, there you are.
I'm delighted to see you.
Why don't you explain our
relationship to these skeptics,
as they don't seem to believe me?
Yes, of course.
As I recall, our relationship is that
you provide me with money and I keep it.
Huh?
I've already spent it all.
Thank you, though.
That old Greg really thought that
Komurasaki fell in love with him?!
What a joke!
Huh?
They're a problem?
Is this geezer bothering you? Huh?
Just give me the word.
The boss Kyoshiro.
I see.
So you're the filthy old stalker who's
been harassing Komodosaki lately.
Our love was not fictitious.
Believe me.
Please, Komodosaki, tell him the truth.
I beg you, don't tell me
this was all for naught.
The sacrifices I made,
there's nothing left.
I threw away everything I had.
It was all for you.
You're one of many, old-timer.
We can't let you cry here.
It's bad for business.
Time to go.
Having some trouble standing up?
We can help.
Get lost.
You got ripped off.
Get on to me.
Stop! Please!
Get up now!
I'm leaving!
I'm sorry!
Go, Murasaki!
The top Oiran's procession
is coming through!
Make way for her passage!
Lady Komurasaki!
That's her!
Are you guys seeing this too?
She's so beautiful!
Whoa, her glove!
Kuburasaki!
I sold my house and family to be with you!
Give it back to me, you swindler!
I trusted you!
Return the gift you gave to me?
You are pathetic.
To me, men are nothing more
than dogs that fetch me riches.
With nothing left to give
me, you are worthless.
There's no escaping now.
Don't give us trouble, you peasants.
There's no place in the Flower
Capital for you lousy deadbeats.
In the name of Shogun Orochi,
we banish you from here!
Please have mercy on me!
None of us are suited for
living outside of the city!
Dem you all to hell! Komurasaki!
Sorry, your pleas fall upon deaf ears.
I resent the poor.
Open the case!
The Oiran Komurasaki has arrived!
So, you got a little
sister out there, Momo?
Manners Tama, who do you think I am?
You should address me properly.
Your momo.
Just forget it.
Yes, I do have one.
She would be 26 years old now.
While some have witnessed
my mother's death,
none have been able to confirm Hiyori's.
She lives!
I have faith my sister's
out there somewhere.
I only pray that she is safe.
Well, I hope you get to meet her soon.
I certainly don't.
If her identity is known, Then
Orochi will set his sights on her.
I cannot seek her out until
we have claimed our victory!
You were late because you were gawking at
the Oiron, and you want me to excuse that?
Guilty as charged, boss.
Do you think you can forgive me?
I was in awe.
Never saw someone so pretty.
On one hand, I can't
really blame you, big guy.
But honor dictates that you need to respect
the fact that I'm your superior here.
You're right.
I'm sorry about that.
I never meant to bring dishonor
to the name of Minatomo,
the legendary Master Carpenter.
Since you work ten times harder
than most, you get a freebie.
But don't make this crap a habit. Hey,
since we're on the topic of that,
how about you show me
the Onigashima Mansion
blueprints and I'll work 20 times as hard.
No, wait.
How does a hundred times
the efficiency sound?
I almost forgot.
You keep on asking me about those.
I had something I wanted to
tell you concerning them.
One second. Let's see.
Gotta clear the honker
before we get to that.
Hang on.
I know where I saw him last.
Pawned those suckers
off about ten years ago.
Why do you think I was
slaving away under you, huh?
Are you senile or were
you just lying to me?
Damn it, kid.
What's the big idea?
You must think really highly of yourself.
To put your hands on the master carpenter.
you ungrateful Long!
I'll never get that time back!
Suck on this!
Franosuke Rocket Launcher!
You're fired!
You take your sorry ass out of here!
I'm happy to!
I don't need this job!
You're asking me about a
pawn from ten years ago?
Don't know.
we rarely take blueprints in honestly
does ring a bell though yeah and
they're still here I'm afraid not
if I recall correctly they're gone
but it's been quite a while let me think
oh
yeah
the guy from the
tenement he was looking to study
them Kamakiri who the hell's that guy
Kamakiri the mansion outline yeah
i did have one of those things at
one point but then i wanted to
follow behind on my rent my landlord
took them from me kobe now who's
this old dude kobe i do recall them
they were quite remarkable so I gifted
them away to my favorite geisha, Kisagawa.
Know her?
Why would I?
I used them as dish
mats till I got scolded.
Someone named Tokujito
took them away from me.
All right, so what's their deal?
They were stolen.
Rocket said they were worth a
great deal and ran off with them.
Okay, that can't be what he looks like.
That is a camel.
Yeah, I'm Rocket.
All that blueprint crap brought me
nothing but headaches and trouble.
Some dirty bastard made
off with him in the end.
I didn't get to see his face, but
he mentioned he came from Cootie.
You sure?
More than certain.
It's Sea Bream.
Must be a new breed or something.
Thank you for your purchase.
Greetings, Surfer Nose Kid.
you seem full of energy all damn
day hey what are you selling there
can't you tell i'm a fishmonger
you're sticking out way too much you
got a whole audience of kids i
couldn't help but notice but why were
you in such a rush just now were you
seeking assistance with something
actually never mind what
i said about sticking
out there's a problem my plan to get those
blueprints were a total
bust i've been chasing
down the damn things all
day let's begin inspecting
the swords we've gathered thus far is that
so that's quite the
development you believe
they're in cootie right
now uh-huh but i hit
a dead end on the trail
got no more leads man i
don't know what to do
with this point regardless
thanks for trying i can take over please
go support the other
missions about the capital
you got it click hmm
now who would want the
layout of kaito's mansion
besides us could it be
we
stole as much as
possible the food of course
and these weapons as
well excellent work and
one of the other part
It's been taken care of.
We're sure it's okay, though.
Aren't we gonna just make
the Beast Pirates really mad
at our Shit Doji by leaving
the notes saying he did it?
That is precisely the plan.
We shall goad him into fighting.
He will have no other choice but to defend
himself once they seek revenge on him.
We need to force him
to reignite his spirit.
The man has suffered a lot the
past two decades, hasn't he?
This feels a bit too
high-handed, if you ask me.
Perhaps so.
Our method may be dishonest, but he's
an invaluable asset for defeating Kaido.
We need his help to ensure our victory!
And with that, we are here!
Yoo-hoo!
I'm back, everyone!
Oh? Hello!
Oh, I didn't expect to
see you yet, Tonoyasu.
Hey there, Yasuie.
It's always a pleasure.
Still no food, though.
I'm hungry.
It hurts.
What the hell's going on?
Yeah, they're laughing.
Wow, very astute.
You noticed already.
We love a good chuckle.
The hukaburitan seems
dreary by comparison.
Of all the living creatures in the
world, only a human can laugh, right?
Best of all, it's free, so
why waste a beautiful thing?
Life is lousy, laugh it off!
Forgive the intrusion!
Chaka!
Oh, don't be so reserved.
Now raise your heads for me.
Let's see what you've
made for dinner tonight.
Sir, we're confident
that you will enjoy it.
Bring it over.
We carefully selected
hands from the Orochi farm.
Then our chefs gently
prepared them in a light boil.
Oh, I don't want chicken.
Right, we shall discard them.
Now take it away.
Next up, we've gathered the
most fresh and ripe vegetables.
Not in the mood. Dispose of it.
Here.
Perhaps some fatty, sorry, might
appease your distinguished palate.
That does sound delightful.
Pair it with tuna sashimi.
I'd settle for nothing less.
What else?
We also brought you a
hand-selected variety of
Sexy from across the land
of Wano Enough already!
I'm more concerned about
the assortment of women
you've brought me What
about my entertainment?
That was a top priority, sir.
Good, good!
Mama!
My tummy!
Mine hurts too!
Look at that!
I've lost another tooth
from lack of nourishment!
Not liking it in him anyway!
Yasuie, why don't you introduce
us to your new rodent friend?
Two, three, did you bring
extras in case you break them?
Check that out!
He's a triple threat!
Oh, full-size Cotton, too!
That for a comedy bit!
Whoa, whoa, whoa!
Try not to scare him off, all right?
I'm proud of my cat.
Oh, my, I'm sorry our local weirdo
won't leave you be. Poor boy.
But I'm still the world's
greatest sycophant, you know?
Can you even believe this guy?
What an upstanding fellow, I tell you.
I find him kind of scary, like a bear.
Good, sir.
Smile more.
Your whole life's ahead of you.
There we go.
Besides, something great has happened
to our trashy little town today.
I know what that means.
A certain someone came to
visit again, didn't he?
None other than Ushimitsu, Koza.
You just barely missed him.
Now, that is lucky.
Oh, he really?
Yes, always seems to know
the right time to drop by.
Though no one knows who
that mystery man is.
He visits every so often,
showing up in the dead
of night after stealing
gold from the wicked
nobles of the capital.
Before vanishing into the dark,
he spreads it around the slum.
What a kind soul, he's so sweet.
Thank goodness for whoever he is.
Fortune comes to those who can laugh.
We were able to pull the money together
and get a little treat thanks to him.
What kind of treat?
You're not going to believe
this! Come here! Look! Look!
I brought you a cup.
You should have some, too.
It's clean water.
We got it for the town with the money.
I'll pass, but thank you.
Just take it.
Don't you worry.
It won't make you feel yucky
like our normal water does.
You must be here for a reason, mister.
Yasuie saw something good in you.
You heard the girl, didn't you?
Drink up, don't be shy.
You're our guy, don't question us why.
Clean and so yummy.
Good for your Tommy.
Clean and so yummy!
Good for your tummy!
It's the spot, huh?
Feel it through your body?
so serious.
Here, let me assist you.
Browns will chase the good fortune away.
Let me tell you about our secret, okay?
In this country, we have a name
for our trademark grin. You ready?
We probably call it the Emmys' Smile.
It's where the place gets its name.
Poverty can't steal our smile.
There's no use crying when we get dying.
Yeah, life is lousy.
Laugh it off.
Bring them to me! Right now.
Right, as you say. But, sir!
What do we have here?
Such beauty.
Ooh.
Do they meet your satisection, my lord?
Indeed, they do.
Gorgeous.
They're perfect.
The banquet may commence now!
Drink, dance, and sing!
Let us be merry!
Sorry for the delay.
Hey, I'm over here, Oko Murasaki.
How nice it is to see you, my lord.
Oh, it is.
Oh, my.
Hey, Traffy, why are you here?
It's an emergency.
Let's bail, Blackleg.
We gotta go.
Is it about the fight before?
I'll kick their ass
again if they come back.
That's not it.
People who know our
faces are on their way.
Hawkins, huh?
That we can handle.
But he's got backup with him.
The Toby Rope are the top six headliners.
They sent two.
Don't mess with them.
Who are they?
The first is page one
I'm afraid to ask who's the other
that's Diaz Drake no more questions.
We'd better start moving
You don't say.
One of the worst generation, huh?
Page one, why must we
stoop to this lowly task?
Need it spelled out?
It's to set an example,
to show what happens to someone stupid
enough to set foot in the land of one.
And ballsy enough to
cross the beast, pirates!
Really?
Where are you here then, Hawkins?
I'm in search of a particular man.
You'll find this mission to be more
than you bargained for. Believe me.
Oh, yoo-hoo!
Buddy, think it over yet?
Hey, you're planning on busting out, yeah?
I know you've got a heart.
Just give in and let me tag along.
think of the benefits if we team
up not a soul could get in our
way oh shut it go fuck jaggy to
be your partner ally with kid
no thank you his entire reputation
is tanked you hear he tried
to go after big mom and fell
miserably no one wants to go anywhere
near that rumors aren't good
either they say the loser's arm
wasn't ripped off by the old bag
herself but by one of her weaker
underlings way
it's true though
I heard it directly from a
very reliable source scalp's
honor either your source is full of
crap or you need to get your
ears checked you heard wrong I
went to a turf but never to fight
big mom hey kid good see ya for
the record I beat one of her sweet
generals I went there to steal
something and I made off with it
fine I believe ya but your arm
is yeah what about my arm I
lost it in a battle against the
red-haired pirates before all
that junk went down need any more
facts that's straight no good then
let me be clear about something
else so listen up you're stupid
monkey this is It's my victory!
I'll be the one that takes down Kaido!
He's gonna be me!
He's mine!
Oh, my God! Chouchou!
Listen here!
The festival draws closer, but
the celebration starts now!
Rejoice!
Let's enjoy ourselves in
this great land of water!
No!
Indulge till your heart's full!
This is the closest you'll
get to heaven in this world!
Pardon us!
We have intel!
A ship is approaching
from the southeast side!
Can't believe she really came here.
That old shrew.
Take this, ship!
Let her and her family
be swallowed by the sea.
I'll tell everyone to unleash
their attacks then, sir.
Don't let that hang in this country.
They've wrangled a koi fish into
pulling their vessel upstream.
They what?
How do they know about the method
we use to climb the waterfall?
Well, uh,
when it comes to gathering intelligence,
they say Big Mom's the
best in the business!
I don't care!
Shut your mouth!
I suppose we knew they
were coming either way.
Just seek her ship already!
That crazy witch.
I made it crystal clear!
She may be old, but she's not senile.
You showed up, Lin-Lin, and now you die!
Let's go.
Oh, my God.
You're not getting away from
me that easily, Straw Hat.